

## **CONTACT DETAILS**



shrideshmukh1001@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/shrishailya-deshmukh/

https://shrideshmukh.github.io

## SKILLS SUMMARY

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Invision Studio
- Adobe XD

# **SHRISHAILYA DESHMUKH**

# SENIOR UI DESIGNER

## **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

UI Designer Specialist with 4+ years of experience in the management of the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery. Skilled with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, Invision studio and web design applications (HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap).

# **ROLES & RESPONSIBILITIES**

- Build storyboards to conceptualize designs and convey project plans to clients and management
- Conduct testing of completed applications, websites, and software to assess user experience
- Create, improve and use wireframes, prototypes, style guides, user flows, and effectively communicate your interaction ideas using any of these methods.
- Continually keep me and my design team updated with the latest changes in our industry's standards.
- Create Web-related design like Website theme,
  Web Application Design, Mobile App UI design,
  Wireframe Design, Prototype Design
- Convert PSD to HTML Web pages
- · Create static and dynamic web pages
- Created interactive designs for complex web applications by way of page/user flow diagrams, site maps, and interactive wireframes.
- Consult with tech startups to review current products and provide design solutions to solve user needs and business challenges through user research, visual design, and prototyping

#### **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION**

- Bachelor Of Computer Science and Engineering from BMIT, Solapur 2015
- Completed Diploma in Computer Science from Collage of engineering, Pandharpur 2011
- Completed 10th From Sangola Vidyamandir, Sangola in 2008

#### **PERSONAL INFO**

**Permeant Address** - At/post-Mahud, Tal-Sangola Dist-Solapur

Gender- Male

Marital Status - Married

Date of Birth- 01/04/1993

Passport No - L8313036

#### **Hobbies** -

Travelling, Reading, playing Cricket

## Language's known -

English, Hindi,

Marathi.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES**

- Software Testing Course From Seed Infotech, Pune.
- HTML5 From SoloLearn.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Senior UI Designer**

Terse Software Pvt Ltd | Nov 2018 - present

- Research new user interface paradigms and develop and maintain style guidelines to support Mobile, WebCreate functional, and technical application documents.
- As a Senior UI Designer, I am responsible to ensure the successful delivery Of the project by managing the process
- Create UX workflow, run quick prototypes, and conduct usability testing.
- Design a logo, Newsletter, Brochure, Branding, Publication
- Create a web page using HTML, CSS, javascript, jquery, new version bootstrap

# **UI Developer**

Arinjay Trading Pvt Ltd | Feb 2018 - Nov 2018

- Gathering and evaluating user requirement in collaboration with the project manager
- Presenting UI design concepts to the project stakeholders for review and feedback.
- Driving the development and communication of clear design guidelines, pattern, Libraries.
- Working closely with the development team to implement the vision.
- Re-designing UI for Android, iOS.

# **UI/UX Designer**

Ideasailor Technolgies Pvt Ltd | Jun 2016 - Feb 2018

- Working according to Product Development's Sprint schedule and providing timely high fidelity prototypes to Engineering
- Work independently and collaboratively with team members to develop UI/UX workflow and design
- Provide QA & feedback to developers
- Create an effective design using front ned technologies as well as tools
- Re-designing UI for Android, iOS.
- Collaborate with developers, product managers, QA, and marketing to create amazing user interfaces